Meta Open Source - Privacy Policy
=================================

_Effective Date: April 25, 2023_

This Privacy Policy describes Meta Platforms, Inc. (**"Meta"**, **"we"**, **"us"** or **"our"**) practices for handling your information in connection with this website and our open source-related websites (**"Websites"**) and any content, related documentation, information and services (e.g. apps, tutorials, tools to support the developer workflow, access to resources, etc.) made available to you on this website (collectively, the **"Services"**). This Privacy Policy describes the personal information we process to support our Services.

For clarity, this Privacy Policy only applies to the Websites and does not apply to any:

1. use of open source code, documentation or specifications made available on GitHub, which are governed by the terms of the applicable open source license;
2. pull requests, issues and any other interactions or features related to participation in open source projects on GitHub, which are governed by GitHub's terms and conditions; or
3. use of any other Meta website, service or product, which are governed by the terms and conditions applicable to those offerings.

#### What Kinds of Information Do We Collect?

When you interact with us through our Services, we may collect or receive the following types of information:

**_Information you provide directly to us._** For certain activities, we may collect the following types of information:

* **_Contact information,_** such as name, email address and contact details; and
* **_Other information_** you provide to us, such as when you send us correspondence or otherwise participate on the Services.

**_Information we collect automatically._** Depending on the type of device you use and how you interact with us, we may also collect certain information automatically when you use our Services, such as:

* **_Device attributes,_** including information such as the operating system, hardware and software versions, battery level, signal strength, available storage space, browser type, app and file names and types, and plugins.
* **_Device operations,_** including information about operations performed on the Services as well as pages visited.
* **_Identifiers,_** including information such as unique identifiers, device IDs, and other identifiers, and Family Device IDs associated with the same device or account.
* **_Network and connections,_** information such as the name of your mobile operator or ISP, language, time zone, mobile phone number, IP address, connection speed, information about other devices that are nearby or on your network, and Wi-Fi hotspots you connect to using our Services.
* **_Cookie data,_** data from cookies and other similar technologies that are stored on your device, including cookie IDs and settings. Learn more about how we use cookies by reading our [Cookie Policy](https://opensource.fb.com/legal/cookie-policy).

**_Information you provide to us through our app (where applicable)._** Some of our Services include the provision of an app. In such cases, we may receive certain video and text content that you choose to provide to us through our app. We may analyze this depending on the context and content in accordance with the purposes described below.

**_Integrations with other services from third parties._** Some of our Services allow you to enable or log in via various online services (collectively, **"Login Services"**). By including these Login Services, we aim to make your online experiences richer and more personalized. When you add a Login Service account to our Services or log in to our Services using such an account, we may collect relevant information necessary to enable our Services to facilitate your login, such as your email address. We may also share your information with that Login Service to facilitate or enhance the delivery of that platform or our Services.

As part of an integration with a Login Service, that Login Service may provide us with access to certain information that you have provided to their platform, and we will use, store, and disclose such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. However, please remember that the manner in which platforms use, store, and disclose your information is governed by the policies that apply to those platforms. Information collected by Login Services is subject to their own terms and policies, not this one.

**_Social media features._** Our Services may use social media features, such as the Facebook "like" button, the "Tweet" button and other sharing widgets (**"Social Media Features"**). You may be given the option by such Social Media Features to post information about your activities on a website to a profile page of yours that is provided by a third party social media network in order to share with others within your network. Social Media Features are either hosted by the respective social media network or hosted directly on our Websites. To the extent the Social Media Features are hosted by the respective social media network(s) and you click through to these from our Websites, the latter may receive information showing that you have visited our Websites. If you are logged in to your social media account, it is possible that the respective social media network can link your visit to our Websites with your social media profile. Your interactions with Social Media Features are governed by the privacy policies of the companies providing the relevant Social Media Features.

#### Cookies and Similar Technologies

Cookies are small pieces of text used to store information on web browsers. Cookies are used to store and receive identifiers and other information on computers, phones and other devices. We use cookies and similar technologies, for such things as maintaining and monitoring the infrastructure of the Services, ensuring security protections, analyzing how our Services perform and other analytics purposes, and fulfilling other legitimate purposes as further described in this Privacy Policy. We also use analytics cookies to better understand how our Services are being used by tracking how you interact with the Services and where you click.

We use cookies served by Google Analytics to collect limited data directly from end-user browsers to enable us to better understand your use of the Services, including making use of the demographics and interests reports services of Google Analytics. Further information on how Google collects and uses this data, including processing in the United States, can be found at [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). You can opt-out of all Google supported analytics within the Services by going to the following webpage: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

Learn more about how we use cookies by reading our [Cookie Policy](https://opensource.fb.com/legal/cookie-policy).

#### How Do We Use Information?

We will use the information described above for the purpose of operating and providing the Websites and our Services. Specifically, we will use the information for the following purposes:

* **_Provide, personalize and improve our Services._** We use your information to provide the Websites and fulfill your requests for resources, services, and information; analyze content that you provide to us and provide suggestions for what is in such content; analyze the use of the Services and user data to understand, improve and operate the Services; and customize the content you see when you use the Services;
* **_Communicate with you._** We use your email address to communicate with you about the Services and let you know about our terms and policies. If you subscribe to a newsletter, we will use your email address to send you such newsletter. We also use your information to respond to you when you contact us;
* **_Promote safety, integrity and security._** We use the information that we have to verify accounts and activity, combat harmful conduct, maintain the integrity of our Services, and promote safety and security on our Websites. For example, we use data that we have to investigate suspicious activity or breaches of the [Terms of Use](https://opensource.fb.com/legal/terms);
* **_For any other purposes_** disclosed to you at the time we collect your information or pursuant to your consent.

#### How We Share Information

There are certain circumstances in which we may share your information with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below:

* **_Service providers and third-party vendors._** We share your information with third-party vendors and service providers that support the Services, for example cloud hosting providers (to provide data storage and processing services), communications providers (to process new queries and to manage our emails) and analytics providers to perform analysis on the Services. These service providers are limited from using your information for any purpose other than to perform services for us.
* **_Legal purposes._** We may disclose information for legal purposes, such as to respond to subpoenas, court orders, legal process, law enforcement requests, legal claims or government inquiries, detect fraud, and to protect and defend the rights, interests, safety, and security of Meta, our affiliates, owner, users, or the public.
* **_Business transfers._** We may share your information in connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of a website, a merger, consolidation, asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.
* **_With your consent._** We may share information for any other purposes disclosed to you at the time we collect the information or pursuant to your consent. If you choose to engage in public activities on the Websites, you should be aware that any information you share there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these areas. You should use caution in disclosing personal information while participating in these areas. We are not responsible for the information you choose to submit in these public areas.

#### Children's Information

Meta does not knowingly collect or store information from children under the age of 13, unless permitted by law. We will delete any information we may have inadvertently received from a child under 13 upon notice. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided personal information to Meta through our Services please contact us.

#### Third-Party Links

Our Websites may contain links to other sites that we do not own or operate (e.g. GitHub). Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, we do not provide your information to these third parties without your consent. The linked websites have separate and independent privacy statements, notices and terms of use, which we recommend you carefully review. We do not have any control over such websites, and therefore have no liability or responsibility for the linked websites' personal information practices.

#### Data Retention

We retain information relating to the Services until it is no longer necessary to serve the purposes for which it was collected, such as to provide the Services to you or improve the Services. Reasons we may retain some information for longer periods include:

* A legal request or obligation, including obligations of Meta Companies or to comply with applicable law;
* A governmental investigation;
* An investigation of possible violations of our terms or policies;
* To prevent harm;
* For safety, security and integrity purposes;
* To protect ourselves, including our rights, property or products;
* If it's needed in relation to a legal claim, complaint, litigation or regulatory proceedings.

#### Additional Information for United States Residents

If you are a United States resident, you can learn more about the consumer privacy rights that may be available to you by reviewing the [United States Regional Privacy Notice](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/policies/uso).

#### Additional Information for Individuals in the European Region and the United Kingdom

If you are a user in a territory or country listed below (the "European Region") or the United Kingdom, the following information also applies to you and supplements the information contained above in the Privacy Policy.

Andorra, Austria, Azores, Belgium, Bulgaria, Canary Islands, Channel Islands, Croatia, Czech Republic, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, France, French Guiana, Germany, Greece, Guadeloupe, Hungary, Iceland, Ireland, Isle of Man, Italy, Latvia, Liechtenstein, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Madeira, Malta, Martinique, Mayotte, Monaco, Netherlands, Norway, Poland, Portugal, Republic of Cyprus, Réunion, Romania, San Marino, Saint Barthélemy, Saint-Martin, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, and Vatican City and the UK sovereign bases in Cyprus (Akrotiri and Dhekelia).

If you live in the European Region, the data controller responsible for your information when you use the Websites is Meta Platforms Ireland Ltd. If you live in the United Kingdom, the data controller responsible for your information when you use the Websites is Meta Platforms, Inc.

**_Our legal basis for processing data._** We collect, use and share data in the ways described above based on the following:

* **_Contractual necessity._** The majority of the processing of personal data described in this Privacy Policy is justified on the basis that it is necessary for the performance of a contract and specifically, for the purposes of our [Terms of Use](https://opensource.fb.com/legal/terms). For example, we rely on this legal basis to create your account, grant you access to our Services and to communicate with you regarding the Services.
* **_Legitimate interests._** Our processing of personal data as described in this Privacy Policy is justified on the basis that it is necessary for the legitimate interests or the legitimate interests of a third party, where not outweighed by your interests or fundamental rights and freedoms. We rely on this legal basis to further understand who is accessing and using the Services; prevent and address fraud, unauthorized use of the Services, breaches of our terms and policies, or other harmful or illegal activity; protect ourselves (including our rights, property or products), our users or others, including as part of investigations or regulatory enquiries; or to prevent death or imminent bodily harm.
* **_Compliance with a legal obligation._** We rely on this legal basis for processing data when the law requires it, including, for example, if there is a valid legal request for certain data.

**_Data Transfers._** We transfer personal data both internally within Meta and externally with our partners. Information controlled by Meta Platforms Ireland Ltd. or Meta Platforms, Inc. may be transferred or transmitted to, or stored and processed in, the United States or other countries for the purposes described in this policy. These data transfers are necessary to provide the services set forth in the [Terms of Use](https://opensource.fb.com/legal/terms).

Meta Platforms Ireland Ltd. will protect your data when it is transferred outside the European Region by implementing appropriate safeguards to protect your personal data, where required, such as using the European Commission's Standard Contractual Clauses for the transfer of personal data outside the EEA. Meta Platforms, Inc. will protect your data when it is transferred to countries outside of the United Kingdom by implementing appropriate safeguards to protect your personal data, where required, such as using the International Data Transfer Agreement or the International Data Transfer Addendum which have been approved by the UK Parliament.

**_Your Rights_**

Under the GDPR and UK GDPR, you have the right to data portability, right to access, right to rectify, and right to erase your data under certain circumstances. You also have the right to object to and restrict certain processing of your data. In evaluating an objection, we will evaluate several factors, including: reasonable user expectations; the benefits and risks to you and third parties; and other available means to achieve the same purpose that may be less invasive and do not require disproportional effort. Your objection will be upheld and we will cease processing your information, unless continued processing is based on compelling legitimate grounds or is needed for legal reasons.

Please note that to protect your information, we may need to verify your identity before processing your request. In some cases, we may need to collect additional information to verify your identity, such as a government issued ID. To exercise your rights under the GDPR or UK GDPR, you can email opensource@meta.com or contact us by mail at the address provided below.

**_Contact information for individuals in the European Region only_**

The data controller responsible for your information is Meta Platforms Ireland Ltd., which you can contact by writing to:

Meta Platforms Ireland Ltd.  
ATTN: Privacy Operations  
Merrion Road  
Dublin 4, D04 X2K5  
Ireland

Contact the Data Protection Officer for Meta Platforms Ireland Ltd. You also have the right to lodge a complaint with Meta Platforms Ireland Ltd.'s lead supervisory authority, the Irish Data Protection Commissioner, or your local supervisory authority.

**_Contact information for individuals in the United Kingdom only_**

If you are in the United Kingdom, the data controller responsible for your information is Meta Platforms, Inc., which you can contact [online](https://www.facebook.com/help/contact/507739850846588), or by writing to:

Meta Platforms, Inc.  
ATTN: Privacy Operations  
1601 Willow Road  
Menlo Park, CA 94025

Contact the Data Protection Officer for Meta Platforms, Inc. You also have the right to lodge a complaint with the UK's Information Commissioner's Office.

#### Changes to this Policy

We will notify you before we make material changes to this Policy. If we make non-material changes, we may update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice.

We recommend that you review the Privacy Policy each time you visit the Websites to stay informed of our privacy practices. Any changes will be effective when we post the revised policy.

#### Questions

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our practices, please contact us at [opensource@meta.com](mailto:opensource@fb.com) or by mail at:

Meta, Inc.  
ATTN: Privacy Operations  
1601 Willow Road  
Menlo Park, CA 94025

* * *

Table of contents[](#undefined)[](#undefined)[](#undefined)[](#undefined)[What Kinds of Information Do We Collect?](#what-kinds-of-information-do-we-collect)[Cookies and Similar Technologies](#cookies-and-similar-technologies)[How Do We Use Information?](#how-do-we-use-information)[How We Share Information](#how-we-share-information)[Children's Information](#childrens-information)[Third-Party Links](#third-party-links)[Data Retention](#data-retention)[Additional Information for United States Residents](#additional-information-for-united-states-residents)[Additional Information for Individuals in the European Region and the United Kingdom](#additional-information-for-individuals-in-the-european-region-and-the-united-kingdom)[Changes to this Policy](#changes-to-this-policy)[Questions](#questions)

Follow Us

Site Map[Projects](https://opensource.fb.com/projects)[FAQ](https://opensource.fb.com/get-involved#faq)[About](https://opensource.fb.com/about)[Get Involved](https://opensource.fb.com/get-involved)

Information[Blog](https://developers.facebook.com/blog/open_source/)[Linux](https://opensource.fb.com/linux)[Careers](https://metacareers.com/)[Bug Bounty Program](https://bugbounty.meta.com/)

Connect[GitHub](https://github.com/facebook)[FB for Developers](https://developers.facebook.com/)

Follow Us

* * *

© 2024 Meta
